<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andy Beck</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andy Beck</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Andy&#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>/posts/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my blog! Not sure exactly what&amp;rsquo;ll end up comprising the content of this section of my personal webpage, but I imagine that posts will cover topics that I am interested in. This could very well include statistics, population and medical genetics, running, and perhaps even some hot takes on pop culture (unlikely, but never say never!)
So buckle up, and get ready to enjoy the ride! (Don&amp;rsquo;t hold your breath waiting on new posts though)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Andy is a PhD student in the Department of Biostatistics at the University of Michigan School of Public Health. He is also a GSRA working with professors Jun Li and Sebastian Zöllner on questions arising at the intersection of population genetics and genomics, and in particular they are interested in modeling and understanding the consequences of variation in the germline mutation rate across the genome.
When he&amp;rsquo;s not dredging through data or debugging code, Andy enjoys running, reading (things other than papers and textbooks), and playing with dogs (and sociable cats).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me, @johndoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Page under construction. In the meantime, check out what I&amp;rsquo;m up to on github!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>